<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<scripts>
  <intro>
    <text>
      In this level we will be discussing everything you need to know about the Distributor Grid Operator (DGO).
      
      As you can see in the picture above, all the houses are grouped by cubes that have a different color.
      
      This is because in reality, every region has a designated DGO. Therefore you can't choose your DGO, you get assigned a DGO.
      
      The DGO is responsible for a number of things, such as: Maintaining the grid (e.g. fixing a Transformatorcabin), taking your meter readings in your house.
      
      To accomplish all of these tasks, you need workers. But ofcourse workers can only be assigned to one task at a time, or you can deploy multiple workers to a single task to decrease the amount of time the problem will take to solve.
      
      But be careful! If new problems occur and you don't have any available workers, you will get power outages and happiness will decrease!
    </text>
  </intro>
  <ui>
    <text>
      Let's explain your user interface.
      
      On the right side below you can see a slider, this is the happiness slider. It represents how happy your customers are.
      
      On the left side of the slider you can see the money panel. It will simply display how much money you have.

      On the left side of the money panel you can see the worker panel. It will display how many workers of your total amount of workers are available.
      
      By clicking on the worker panel, you will open the Worker Menu.
    </text>
  </ui>
  <worker>
    <text>
      If you want to buy more workers, you will need to earn money by solving problems that will occur throughout the game.
    </text>
  </worker>
  <events>
    <text>
      During the game you will get events. If you choose to accept this event, a popup will appear and will ask you a question regarding DGO's. If you decline, happiness will decrease since you are not solving problems.

      If a question is answered correctly, one of two things can happen. A random problem that you are solving will either be instantaniously solved OR the time remaining to solve that problem will be halved.

      If a question is answered incorrectly, one of two things can happen. A new random problem will occur that you will have to solve OR the time remaining to solve an exisiting random problem will be doubled.
    </text>
  </events>
</scripts>