<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<scripts>
  <intro>
    <text>
      In this level we will be discussing everything you need to know about the DGO.
      
      As you can see in the picture above, different groups of houses have a different colored cube above them.
      
      This indicates that every group has a different DGO and that you can't choose your DGO, you get a DGO assigned to you or the place that you live.
      
      But for the sake of the game, you will control 'all' DGO's.

      The main goal of this level is to solve a variety of problems that will occur.
      
      e.g. taking the meter readings from your customers, fixing substations and transformer cabins etc.
      
      This can be achieved by deploying 'Workers' to solve your problems.
      
      Problems will take time to be solved, but you can always deploy more workers to a certain problem to decrease the duration of that problem.
      
      Make sure you always have some workers ready in case of a major problem.
    </text>
  </intro>
  <ui>
    <text>
      Let's explain your user interface.
      
      On the right side below you can see a slider, this is the happiness slider. This indicates how happy your customers are with your ability to solve problems.

      On the left side of the slider you can see the money panel. It will simply display how much money you have.
      
      On the left side of the money panel you can see the worker panel. This shows how many workers of your total amount of workers are available for work.
      
      By clicking on the worker panel, you will open the recruitment panel. Here you will be able to buy more workers for you to deploy and solve problems.
    </text>
  </ui>
  <recruitment>
    <text>
      If you want to buy more workers, you can go to the recruitment center by clicking on the worker panel on the right side below.

      Here you can buy a new worker, but every worker you buy will come at an increased cost!
    </text>
  </recruitment>
  <events>
    <text>
      During the game you will get events. A problem will occur for you to solve. You can choose to accept this problem, or you can decline it.
      
      By declining it, happiness will decrease. By accepting it and not solving it, happiness will also decrease. By accepting it and solving it, you will earn money you can spend on extra workers.

      Some problems will come in the form of a question you need to answer.
      
      If a question is answered correctly, a random problem will be solved, or the remaining time on the problem will be halved, based on the difficulty of the problem.

      If a question is answered incorrectly, the remaining time on a random existing problem will be doubled.
    </text>
  </events>
</scripts>