<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<scripts>
  <meganCanvas>
    <text>Hi and welcome to MeCity! First things first..

A new family moved into this house. Now they need electricity to be able to watch their TV, put on the lightning, charge their phones,...


But.. Who do they need to contact for their need for electricity?

After the introduction you will be able to explore the city :)
    </text>
  </meganCanvas>
  <supplierCanvas>
    <text>Hi, I am the supplier. My task is to sell energy towards the customers. To do this, I buy energy from the producer to pass it through the customers or I can even produce my own energy.

I’m not only responsible for selling energy towards the customers but also for closing contracts with the end-customers. If they agree with the terms and conditions, they can sign a contract for a specific contract duration.
Because of the liberalized market, there are a lot of energy suppliers in the market, this means that I have a lot of competitors. Therefore, it’s important that I have a good customer service, lower administrative costs, … to make sure customers will sign contracts with me and not with other energy suppliers.

To make sure that there’s enough energy bought from the supplier, forecasting the amount of energy, needed in the future, is very important. Another main task that I have is creating and sending out the invoices.

Here is a list of common known suppliers in Belgium:
 - Eneco
 - Engie Electrabel
 - Luminus
 - ...
    </text>
  </supplierCanvas>
  <dgoCanvas>
    <text>
      Hi, nice to meet you! The DGO's (also known as the Distribution Grid Operator) main task is transporting energy (= switching from high voltage to low voltage in case of electricity and switching from high pressure to low pressure for gas) and will then be transferred onto the local distribution network and is delivered to your house or workplace where, in many cases, it will be passed through a meter into your home's network.

      Other responsabilities of the DGO are: maintaining and installing and replacing the electricity and natural gas meters (also budget meters), implementing new connections and editing the existing connections, recording the meter readings, maintaining the public lightning, and many more.
      In the liberalized market, there’s a free choice of supplier but no free choice of DGO.

      The DGO that will be responsible for your house or workplace will depend where the DGO is located. The DGO will be responsible for one specific area in the country.
    </text>
  </dgoCanvas>
  <tgoCanvas>
    <text>The transmission grid operator is responsible for keeping the high voltage transmission system running reliable and efficient. Electricity transmission can be seen as the vital link between the power production and the power usage. Transmission lines carry electricity at high voltages over long distances from power plants to communities.
The main task of the transmission grid operators is transporting the high voltage electricity or high pressure gas over long distances.

Once the electricity, gas or water has been placed on the network it will need to be transported. The transport or transmission over long distances is done using a high pressure or high voltage network which is called the transmission grid. The transmission grid operator is responsible both for maintaining the grid and for the actual transmission of the commodity.
Industrial consumers may use this high voltage electricity or high pressure gas immediately. Examples of big industrial consumers are Bayer or Nike.

But where do we get our energy from?
    </text>
  </tgoCanvas>
  <producer>
    <text>The utility value chain starts with producing and importing energy. This is the responsibility of the producer or the importer. There are two types of energy production: non-renewable and sustainable.

First of all a 'classic' power plant uses oil, gas, coal or uranium to heat water to steam. Also called "gray" electricity because it is produced using fossil, non-renewable fuels.

Secondly, there is also "green" electricity generated by renewable energy sources (solar, wind, biomass, waste, ...).

In the circle at the top right, there are a few examples of producers and importers in Belgium. Electrabel and EDF Luminus are responsible for the bulk of electricity production in Flanders. Some new players have become producers since the liberalisation. The most important being ENI and EON.

Here we can see a nucleair power plant in the game. This will be the source of our energy throughout the game.
    </text>
  </producer>
</scripts>