<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- xml used for the scripts for the producer eventsystem (popups) -->
<scripts>
  <popup>
    <text>
      Oh no! Your forecast for your energy production is wrong!

      What action will you undertake?
    </text>
    <answers>
      <answer influence ="3">Import more energy from other producers.</answer>
      <answer influence ="-2">There is nothing I can do.</answer>
    </answers>
  </popup>
  <popup>
    <text>
      Following the climate protests in Brussels, the Belgian Government has decided to close down all non-renewable energy sources and fully rely on renewable energy. (Implying the government bought enough renewable energy sources to sustain the needs of Belgium.)

      Why is this a bad choice?
    </text>
    <answers>
      <answer influence ="-2">Many people will lose their job, because a lot of power stations will be shutdown.</answer>
      <answer influence ="-1">This is in fact not a bad choice. Relying on renewable energy sources gives us the opportunity to reduce pollution and fight climate change.</answer>
      <answer influence ="3">Because renewable energy sources are not always reliable, and therefore can cause power outages if the produced quota does not meet the consumed quota.</answer>
    </answers>
  </popup>
  <popup>
    <text>
      You have received a new forecast! It indicates that the total amount of energy produced by both your renewable and non-renewable energy sources will be higher than necessary to fulfill the energy consumption for today, but will decrease heavily tomorrow because of a cloudy day.

      What action will you undertake?
    </text>
    <answers>
      <answer influence ="-1" >Decrease/Increase production of my non-renewable energy sources accordingly</answer>
      <answer influence ="2">Leave my non-renewable energy sources be. They will produce too much the 1st day, but will produce enough the 2nd day.</answer>
      <answer influence ="-1">Decrease production of my non-renewable energy sources so I don't have an overproduction on the 1st day.</answer>
    </answers>
  </popup>

  <popup>
    <text>
      The Production of energy through renewable energies does pose quite the challenge.
      As the amount of energy being produced is inconsistent, this will help need to be balanced by input from conventional power stations, which is called ...
    </text>
    <answers>
      <answer influence ="2" >Spinning reserves</answer>
      <answer influence ="-1">Non-spinning reserves</answer>
      <answer influence ="-2">replacement reserves</answer>
    </answers>
  </popup>
  <popup>
    <text>
      BONUS

      How much energy from a coal power plant makes it to customers as electricity?
    </text>
    <answers>
      <answer influence ="-1" >A quarter</answer>
      <answer influence ="1">A third</answer>
      <answer influence ="-1">Half</answer>
      <answer influence ="-1">Two-thirds</answer>
    </answers>
    <note>
      About a third of the energy from a steam coal power plant makes it to customers as electricity. A very efficient type of natural gas plant, called combined cycle, typically converts about 40% of the fuel into electricity,
      with advanced units capable of 60% efficiency.
    </note>
  </popup>
  <popup>
    <text>
      BONUS

      What country is the premier source of steel for nuclear power plants?
    </text>
    <answers>
      <answer influence ="-1" >US</answer>
      <answer influence ="1">Japan</answer>
      <answer influence ="-1">Chile</answer>
      <answer influence ="-1">Scotland</answer>
    </answers>
    <note>
      Japan Steel Works long was the only foundry that could forge a reactor vessel in one piece, seen as essential to reduce risk of leaks.
      But China and Russia now have the capacity, and new facilities are under construction.
    </note>
  </popup>
  <popup>
    <text>
      BONUS

      What global treaty has slashed world greenhouse gas emissions by 11 gigatons a year?
    </text>
    <answers>
      <answer influence ="-1" >The Kyoto protocol</answer>
      <answer influence ="-1" >The United Nations Frakework Convention on Climate Change</answer>
      <answer influence ="1" >The Montreal Protocol</answer>
      <answer influence ="-1" >The United Nations Convention on the Law of the Sea</answer>
    </answers>
    <note>
      The 1990 Montreal Protocol, in phasing out ozone-depleted substances with high global warming potential, had the side benefit of eliminating the equivalent of 11 gigatons a year of carbon dioxide emissions by 2010.
      (about 5 to 6 times the target set for the first period of the Kyoto Protocol on climate change)
    </note>
  </popup>
  <popup>
    <text>
      BONUS

      Estimates of what U.S. fuel resource have grown 40% or more since 2006?
    </text>
    <answers>
      <answer influence ="1" >Natural gas</answer>
      <answer influence ="-1" >Coal</answer>
      <answer influence ="-1" >wind</answer>
      <answer influence ="-1" >Geothermal</answer>
    </answers>
    <note>
      Estimates of U.S. natural gas have grown 40% or more since 2006, thanks to the success of hydraulic fracturing technology, making huge reserves now recoverable.
    </note>
  </popup>
  <popup>
    <text>
      BONUS

      Do any cars run on coal
    </text>
    <answers>
      <answer influence ="-1">Yes</answer>
      <answer influence ="1">No</answer>
    </answers>
    <note>
      No cars run directly on coal, but about 30% of South Africa's transportation needs are met by a diesel fuel that is processed from coal.
      When oil prices soared in the U.S., there was a frenzy of interest in coal-to-liquids there, although there are concerns about its high-carbon intensity.
    </note>
  </popup>
  <popup>
    <text>
BONUS

What solution is said to have potential for 57% of needed carbon cuts by 2030?
    </text>
    <answers>
      <answer influence ="-1" >Space-based solar systems</answer>
      <answer influence ="1">Energy efficiency</answer>
      <answer influence ="-1">Carbon capture and storage</answer>
      <answer influence ="-1">Nanotechnology</answer>
    </answers>
    <note>
      The International Energy Agency's scenario for stabilizing the atmospheric concentration of carbon dioxide at 450 parts per million would get 57% of the cuts from efficiency gains.
    </note>
  </popup>
  <popup>
    <text>
BONUS

Are there any choices for electricity generation that don't rely on water?
    </text>
    <answers>
      <answer influence ="-1">Yes</answer>
      <answer influence ="1">No</answer>
    </answers>
    <note>
      No. Coal, nuclear, natural gas, and solar thermal plants all produce electricity by boiling water into steam to turn turbines. 
      Wind and solar photovoltaic power use much less water, but regular water use is still needed to keep the blades nd panels clean or their operation degrades
    </note>
  </popup>
  <popup>
    <text>
BONUS

Does ethanol always deliver lower fuel economy than gasoline?
    </text>
    <answers>
      <answer influence ="1" >Yes</answer>
      <answer influence ="-1">No</answer>
    </answers>
    <note>
      Yes. Because of ethanol's lower energy content, it takes 1.03 gallons (3.90 liters) of E10 (the most common blend, which is gasoline with 10% ethanol) to travel as far as 1 gallon (3.79 liters) of regular gasoline.
      It takes 1.33 gallons (5.03 liters) if the blend is increased to 85% ethanol
    </note>
  </popup>
  <popup>
    <text>
BONUS

Can solar power provide electricity when the sun isn't shining?
    </text>
    <answers>
      <answer influence ="1" >Yes</answer>
      <answer influence ="-1">No</answer>
    </answers>
    <note>
      Many solar energy systems have battery storage, allowing users to draw energy at night. Large solar thermal power projects are coming online that use molten salt to store energy for use after dark.
    </note>
  </popup>
</scripts>