<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<scripts>
  <popup>
    <text>
Ooh no, a colleague-supplier went bankrupt... You have taken in his customers! Good for you, but..

What do you have to do with your energy supply now?
    </text>
    <answers>
      <answer influence ="3">Go to the energy market and buy new supply</answer>
      <answer influence ="-2">This doesn't change a thing, I just have more customers and more profit</answer>
      <answer influence ="-3">I have more profit now</answer>
    </answers>
  </popup>
  <popup>
    <text>
You get a phone call from a customer. He tells you the whole street has a power outage.

How do you react?
    </text>
    <answers>
      <answer influence ="-2">'We can't help you right now. We are aware of the situation. You will just have to wait a few hours'</answer>
      <answer influence ="-1">'Thanks for letting us know, we are aware of the problem. We are going to see what we can do. Your issue should be resolved in a couple of hours'</answer>
      <answer influence ="3">'Thanks for calling. We will dispatch some technicians to resolve the issue. We will call you back when we have more information. If you have any questions in the meantime, please feel free to contact us'</answer>
    </answers>
  </popup>
  <popup>
    <text>
Incoming phone call: 'Hello, I got an invoice for my electricity usage but I think there's been a mistake. I don't have an MMR meter but a smart meter, so I think the amount of money I have to pay isn't correct.

How do you react?
    </text>
    <answers>
      <answer influence ="2" >'We will check it with the DGO and call you back at a later time. There might have been a mistake during administration. Thanks for calling, we will contact you as soon as possible'</answer>
      <answer influence ="-2">'Hi Madam, you have to call the DGO himself if you have questions about the meter installation. We can’t fix your problem. Have a nice day!'</answer>
      <answer influence ="-3">'Thanks for letting us know. You were registered to have an MMR meter. If you have a smart meter, we will send a technician over as soon as possible to gather the information on your SMR as well as do a meter reading. Many thanks, have a nice day'</answer>
    </answers>
  </popup>

  <popup>
    <text>
The Belgian Red Devils are playing the world cup in Russia. You have to forecast if they are going to win or lose.

If you buy a lot of energy, and Belgium wins, you will have lots of benefits. If they lose, there will be a loss of energy and money. If you play safe and don't buy too much energy (you just want to see and wait if the Belgians are going to win),
you will have to pay double of the prices for the energy. It's up to you!
    </text>
    <answers>
      <answer influence ="2" >You play safe and don't buy too much energy</answer>
      <answer influence ="-1">You choose to have lots of energy</answer>
    </answers>
    <note>
The Belgians have lost, we will conquer the world another time..
    </note>
  </popup>
  <popup>
    <text>
Hi, I have a vacation house in the woods where my invoices are delivered. I didn’t know this was possible. Of course I want my invoices get send to my official home address. Can you fix that?
    </text>
    <answers>
      <answer influence ="-2" >'Hi, yeah, it’s not possible to have 2 adresses the invoices can get send to. I will call you back later, after I have more information. Have a nice day!'</answer>
      <answer influence ="3">'Hi, that can be true because you can have a delivery address and a billing address at the same time. We will adjust your address to the one you prefer. Thanks for calling, have a nice day!'</answer>
    </answers>
  </popup>
  <popup>
    <text>
You are going to invest in a new software program to help your administration:

What do you do?
    </text>
    <answers>
      <answer influence ="-3" >'UMAX by Itinerys: implementation cost estimated to 200.000€ and their solution has a 60% fit with our requirements'</answer>
      <answer influence ="-3">'SAP: implementation cost estimated to 400.000€ and their solution has a 80% fit with our requirements'</answer>
      <answer influence ="3">'MECOMS by MECOMS a Ferranti company: implementation cost estimated to 200.000€ and their solution has a 80% fit with our requirements'</answer>
    </answers>
  </popup>
  <popup>
    <text>
You’ve send out a batch of 10.000 periodic invoices, but there was a bug in your software system.

What are you going to do?
    </text>
    <answers>
      <answer influence ="-1" >'Nothing – ride out the storm'</answer>
      <answer influence ="-3">'Close the company'</answer>
      <answer influence ="3">'Upscale the call centre with extra agents, post messages on social media and website and get in touch with the software vendor for a solution'</answer>
    </answers>
  </popup>
  <popup>
    <text>
A customer calls in to tell us he’s moving out his property.

What are you going to do?
    </text>
    <answers>
      <answer influence ="-3" >'Nothing'</answer>
      <answer influence ="1">'Send him an end note and close the contract'</answer>
      <answer influence ="3">'Send him an end note, close the contract, send the information to market parties who need to know'</answer>
    </answers>
  </popup>
  <popup>
    <text>
We received information from the market that an existing customer of ours has switched to another supplier?

What are you going to do?
    </text>
    <answers>
      <answer influence ="-3" >'Call that customer and tell him he shouldn’t do that'</answer>
      <answer influence ="1">'Send him an end note, close the contract'</answer>
      <answer influence ="3">'Check if it’s a valid switch – if not send a rejection to the market – if yes – send him an end note and close the contract'</answer>
    </answers>
  </popup>
  <popup>
    <text>
We receive measurements for a gas meter.

The measurement is expressed in:
    </text>
    <answers>
      <answer influence ="-1" >'kwh'</answer>
      <answer influence ="3">'M3'</answer>
      <answer influence ="-3">'liters'</answer>
    </answers>
  </popup>
  <popup>
    <text>
We receive measurements for an electricity meter

The measurement is expressed in:
    </text>
    <answers>
      <answer influence ="3" >'kwh'</answer>
      <answer influence ="-3">'M3'</answer>
      <answer influence ="-3">'liters'</answer>
    </answers>
  </popup>
  <popup>
    <text>
We supply electricity and gas to our customers. When a customer uses both and we are sending invoices:
    </text>
    <answers>
      <answer influence ="-1" >'We always send separate invoices for gas and electricity '</answer>
      <answer influence ="1">'We always send one invoice combining gas and electricity '</answer>
      <answer influence ="2">'When possible we send one invoice combining gas and electricity '</answer>
    </answers>
  </popup>
  <popup>
    <text>
In exceptional cases we need to manualy change an invoice.

This costs time. What are you going to about it:
    </text>
    <answers>
      <answer influence ="3" >'It only happens a 2 times per month and the manual change takes 10 minutes – we keep doing so '</answer>
      <answer influence ="1">'We asked our software vendor to automate it – that will cost 50.000€ - we confirmed the change'</answer>
      <answer influence ="-3">'We call these customers and tell them to look for another supplier'</answer>
    </answers>
  </popup>
  <popup>
    <text>
      A Customer calls in because he had a Sauna installed a few months ago (which will most probably have a huge impact on his/her electricity consumption).
      Which kind of invoice could we issue to avoid a very high next periodical invoice?
    </text>
    <answers>
      <answer influence ="3" >'Intermediate Invoice'</answer>
      <answer influence ="-2">'Correction note'</answer>
      <answer influence ="-3">'Incidental note'</answer>
    </answers>
  </popup>

  <popup>
    <text>
      A customer calls in to let the supplier know that he currently cannot pay his bills / invoices.
      What are your options as supplier?
    </text>
    <answers>
      <answer influence ="3" >'Postpone the due dates of the invoices or put together a payment plan '</answer>
      <answer influence ="-3">'Write off the customer'</answer>
      <answer influence ="-3">'Immediately stop delivering energy to the customer'</answer>
    </answers>
  </popup>

  <popup>
    <text>
      A customer calls in to let us know that he went bankrupt, this means we will have to “write off” the invoice, this is a loss we might need to suffer.
    </text>
    <answers>
      <answer influence ="-3" >'Postpone the due dates of the invoices or put together a payment plan '</answer>
      <answer influence ="3">'Write off the open transactions of this customer'</answer>
      <answer influence ="-3">'Immediately stop delivering energy to the customer'</answer>
    </answers>
  </popup>
</scripts>