<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<scripts>
  <intro>
    <text>
      This is the TGO level.

      The TGO or Transmission Grid Operator is responsible for the transmission or transport of high voltage, produced by the producer, to high voltage customers or step down transformers.
      
      The TGO is also responsible for the maintenance of the transmision lines that transport the high voltage.
      
      An example of a TGO in Belgium is Elia, Belgium's electricity transmission system operator.
      
      Core activities of Elia are:
      
      1. infrastructure management: the maintenance and development of the net and the connection of electric installations on the net.
      
      2. system management: granting access to the net, tracking the currents on the net to keep a good overview of the functionality of the net and to achieve a good balance between consumption and production of electricity.
      
      3. market facilitator: development of initiatives to improve the functionality of the electricity market.
      
      Since there isn't much else to say about the TGO, you will be playing minigames that will represent a certain task the TGO has to complete to achieve a good functionality over the net.
    </text>
  </intro>
  <ui>
    <text>
      Let's explain your user interface.
      
      Next to the pause button is the minigames button.
      
      By clicking on the minigames button, you will open the minigames menu where you can select from a variety of minigames.
    </text>
  </ui>
  <memory>
    <text>
      The first minigame is 'memory'. In this minigame you need to find image pairs to earn points.
      
      You can find a pair by turning around 2 images and if they are a pair, they will be removed from the board.
      
      If the 2 images are not a pair, then the image will be turnt over again and you have to select a new pair of images.
    </text>
  </memory>
  <breakout>
    <text>
The second minigame is 'breakout'. In this minigame you control a panel that will redirect a ball to other breakable panels.

To win the game, you have to destroy all other panels.
    </text>
  </breakout>
  <simon-says>
    <text>
The third minigame is 'simon says'. In this minigame you need to repeat a sequence of colors.

After each sequence, a random color is added to the end of the sequence.

You earn points based on the length of the sequence.
    </text>
  </simon-says>
  <mastermind>
    <text>
      The fourth minigame is 'mastermind'. In this minigame you need to guess the 4 colour code.
      
      You can achieve this by choosing 4 colours and after every selection, you get feedback about the correct position or color that are present in your selection.
      
      This feedback can help you decide which colors you need to take next or in what position you need to place them.
    </text>
  </mastermind>
  <hangman>
    <text>
      The fifth minigame is 'hang man'. In this minigame you need to guess the word that is hidden on the screen.
      
      You can achieve this by guessing a letter.
      
      If the letter is correct, then the letter will appear on all spots where it appears in the word.
      
      If the letter is incorrect, then the letter will appear to the side, so you know which letters are incorrect and a piece of a hanging man will appear.
      
      If you guessed incorrectly too many times and the hangman picture is complete, you will lose the game.
    </text>
  </hangman>
  <catcher>
    <text>
      The sixth minigame is 'Catcher'. In this minigame you need to catch as much electricity as you can.
      
      You can achieve this by using the bucket that can move from left to right to catch the electricity.
      
      Every time you catch electricity, the falling speed of the electricity will rise.
      
      This will make the game harder when you have caught a lot of electricity.
    </text>
  </catcher>
</scripts>